Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 26, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Dear Brother George Meany - Correspondence, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: Arne Geijer
  - Item 4: Ekonomiska Ustikter hosten, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Ekonomiska Utsikter hosten, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Ekonomiska Utsikter varen, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Employment Policy in Sweden, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: Gunnar Olsson
  - Item 8: Svenska Metallindustriarbetareforbundets Stadgar, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Swedish Trade Unions and the Social Democratic Party: The Formative Years, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: Donald J. Blake
  - Item 10: XV Meeting of the Orit Executive Committee, Miami, Florida, February 2-5, 1960, Letter to the President and other members of the ICFTU Ad Hoc Committee, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: The Swedish Metalworkers' Union, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Basic Agreement in Sweden between the Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1958; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Facts about SIF, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: Svenska industritjanstemannaforbundet
  - Item 14: Facts about SIF, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Perspective on Labour Conditions in Sweden, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Labor Peace: Sweden's Formula, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Box: 26, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Allmanna Sjukkassor 1961, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Sweden. Riksforsakringsverket
  - Item 2: Agreement concerning Time and Motion Studies concluded by Swedish Employers' Confederation and Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Agreements Regarding Works Councils between the Swedish Employers Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions and between the Swedish Employers Confederation and the Central Organization of Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Svenska arbetsgivareforeningen; Landsorganisationen i Sverige; Tjanstemannens centralorganisation
  - Item 4: Agreements regarding Works Councils between the Swedish Employers Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions and between The Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Central Organization of Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Basic Agreement between the Swedish Employers Confederation and the Swedish Union of Clerical and Technical Employees in Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Basic Agreement between the Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Swedish Union of Clerical and Technical Employees in Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Basic Agreement between the Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Swedish Union of Clerical and Technical Employees in Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Ekonomiska Utsikter varen, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Employment of Women and the Community: Draft Programme on Women's Employment, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Enkat om tjanstemannautbildning I foretagsregi, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations in Sweden - Myth or Model?, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Joseph A. Raffaele
  - Item 12: Swedish Professional Associations as Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Sveriges akademikers centralorganisation
  - Item 13: The Wage Policy of White Collar Worker Unions in Sweden, 1964; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Trade Unions and the Press, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Rune Blomkvist
  - Item 15: Agreement concerning Time and Motion Studies concluded by Swedish Employers Confederation and Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Promoting Mutual Interests on Sweden's Labour Market, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Svenska arbetsgivarefr_eningen; Landsorganisationen i Sverige
  - Item 17: Promoting Mutual Interests on Sweden's Labour Market, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: The Swedish Employers' Confederation, 1958; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: TCO: The Central Organisation of Salaried Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Box: 27, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Collective Agreements and Joint Plant Rules applying to Engineering Plants belonging to The Swedish Metal Trades Employers' Association, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Development of Labour Peace in Sweden, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Author: Stig Gustafsson
  - Item 3: Ekonomiska Utsikter varen 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Labour Legislation in Sweden, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Author: Bertil Bolin
  - Item 5: Social Policy in Sweden- a Survey, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Author: Sven F. Bengtson
  - Item 6: The Agreement on Collective Life Insurance, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Wage Policy in Sweden Theory and Practice, A Trade Union View on Income Policy, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Author: Landsorganisationen I Sverige
  - Item 8: Wage Policy in Sweden Theory and Practice, A Trade Union View on Income Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Sweden, an important market for exporters, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Author: Grossistforbundet
  - Item 11: Valkommen I ganget, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Economic Expansion and Structural Change, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Box: 27, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Basic Agreement between The Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Author: Svenska arbetsgivareforeningen; Landsorganisationen i Sverige
  - Item 2: Der Schwedische Metallindustrierabeiterverband, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Ekonomiska hosten 1967 utsikter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Ekonomiska utsikte, varen 1967, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Ekonomiska Utsikter hosten 1964, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Ekonomiska Utsikter hosten 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Ekonomiska Utsikter varen 1966, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: LO skolornas kursprogram 1965, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Tjanstemannen och Foretagsnamnderna, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Author: Tjanstemannens centralorganisation. Arbetsgruppen for foretagsnamndsfragor
  - Item 10: Fack forenings rorelsen, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Kursverksamheten, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Vara Kurses Hosten 1964 - Varen 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Vara Kurses Hosten 1964 - Varen 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Vara Kurses Hosten 1964 - Varen 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Ekonomiska Utseikter varen 1964, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Box: 27, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employee Involvement in Sweden, 1987; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Christian Bratt
  - Item 2: Important Developments in Scandinavia (particularly Sweden) which influenced the labor movements and systems of industrial relations, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Report by the Netherlands joint team which visited Sweden from 6th-12th September, 1964, to study Active Labour Market Policy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development. Social Affairs Division
  - Item 4: Swedish Trade Unions and Politics, 1973; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Nils Elvander
  - Item 5: The Swedish Labour Market Administration: Organization and Tasks (At head of title: To Our Foreign Readers ), 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Trade Union Funds in Sweden, 1988; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Leif Widen
  - Item 7: Trade Union Organization in the future: Summary of a report to the 1991 LO Congress, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Wage Policy for the Future: Summary of a report to the 1991 LO Congress, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Work and Fulfillment: Summary of a report to the 1991 LO Congress, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Workers' participation in Sweden, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Resolution on Multinationals, 1974; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: De vleesprijzen, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Notes: appear to be newspaper type articles
  - Item 13: Multinational Investment and Global Purpose, 1977; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Lee I. Iacocca (text of remarks)
  - Item 14: Facts about the Swedish Engineering Employees Association, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Author: Sveriges verkstadsforening
- Box: 27, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Demographic and Socio-Economic Data, 1957; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Family Income and Expenditures, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Labor Force and Disability Data, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Labor Force and Socio-Economic Data, 1960; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Labor Force and Socio-Economic Data, 1959; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Philippine StatisticalBulletin: Labor ForceAttainment Data, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Agreement about Enterprise Councils - Swedish Employers' Confederation, Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, Swedish Central Organization of Salaried Employees, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Basic Agreement between the Swedish Employers Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1950; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Constitution of the Swedish Employers Confederation, 1950; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Kollektivavtal mellen Forsvarsvasendets centrala forvaltnings-myndigheter och Forsvarsverkens Civila Personals Forbund, 1944; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Report on the wage-earner funds, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Swedish Industrial Relations System, 1974; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Swedish Textile Employers Association: Collective Agreements for Textile Workers and Other Workers 1948, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: Swedish Textile Employers' Association
  - Item 14: Swedish Textile Employers' Association: Collective Agreements for Textile Workers and Other Workers 1948, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: The Act on the Position of a trade-union representative at the work place, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: Sweden
  - Item 16: The Swedish Act on Co-Determination at Work, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: The Swedish Act on Litigation in Labour Disputes, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: Sweden. Arbetsmarknadsdepartementet.
  - Item 18: This is SAF, 1984; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Wage-Earner Funds - The Swedish Experience, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: Hans-Goran Myrdal
  - Item 20: Collective Agreements 1982 between the Swedish Engineering Employers' Association and the Swedish Metal Workers' Union, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: Sveriges verkstadsforening; Swedish Metal Workers' Union
  - Item 21: La negociation collective en Suisse, Tendances et problemes recents, 1977; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Author: F. Portner
    Language: French.
  - Item 22: The Central Organisation of Salaried Employees: Facts and Figures about a New Movement in Sweden, 1948; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Agreement concerning Time and Motion Studies concluded by Swedish Employers Confederation and Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1949; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: The Swedish Act on Board Representation for the Employees in Joint Stock Companies and Cooperative Associations, 1985; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: The Unions and the Party - A Team, 1984; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Box: 27, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Evening News, Tuesday, August 17, 1951, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Filipino Worker, April 1956 (several articles), Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Filipino Worker, August 1956 (several articles), Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Redhenfchaftsbericht fur die Sabre 1916/1917, 1918; Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Author: Gewerkschaft Nahrung-Genuss-Gaststatten
- Box: 27, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Acord du 19 juillet 1949 entre les organisations de l'industrie des machines et des metaux participant a la convention du 19 juillet 1937/49 sur Le Paiement de Jours d'Absences pour cause de mariage, de naissance, et de deces, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Demographische und Wirtschaftliche Rechnungsgrundlagen zur Eidgenossischen Alters-und Hinterlassenenversicherung, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Author: Ernst Kaiser
  - Item 3: Les Syndicats en Suisse vues sur le passe et le present, 1946; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Author: Edouard Weckerle
  - Item 4: Le Fonds de Compensation de l'Assurance-Vieillesse, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Author: E. Seiler
  - Item 5: Message du Conseil federal a l'Assemblee federale relatif a un projet de loi sur l'assurance-vieillesse et survivants, 1946; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The Trade Unions in Switzerland, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Author: Eduard Weckerle
- Box: 27, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Accord du 19 juillet 1944, 20 decembre 1946 et 19 juillet 1949 entre les organisations de l'industrie des machines et des metaux participant a la Convention du 19 juillet 1937/49, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Accord sur les cotisations des employeurs a l'assurance de l'indemnite journaliere en cas de maladie des ouvriers, 1948; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Die schweizerischen Gewerkschaftsverbande im Jahre 1948: Vier Jahrsehnte nach der Reorganisation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Author: Schweizerischer Gewerkschaftsbund
  - Item 4: Entwicklungstendenzen in der Praxis des Gesamtarbeitsvertrages, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Author: E. Schweingruber
  - Item 5: Les Rentes, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Loi federale sur l'assurance-vieillesse et survivants, 1947; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Message du Conseil federal a l'Assemblee federale concernant le financement, au moyen de fonds publics, de l'assurance-vieillesse et survivants, 1946; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Notre Ecole de contremaitres, 1946; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Programme de travail de l'Union syndicale suisse, 1934; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Statuts de l'Union syndicale suisse, 1946; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Unsere Werkmeisterschule, 1948; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Verabredung: Uber Beitrahe des Arbeitgebers an die Krankeneldverischerung der Arbeiter, 1948; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Box: 27, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Adressen-Verzeichnis 1949/50, 1950; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Annuaire des adresses pour 1949-1950, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Die Gemeinschaft der Tarifparteien, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Author: Beat Kleiner
  - Item 4: Die schweizerischen Gewerkschaftsverbande im Jahre 1955, 1956; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Preparation d'une Loi federale sur les conventions collectives de travail et l'extension de leur champ d'application par decision administrative: Rapport et projet de loi, 1950; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Author: Switzerland. Office federal de l'industrie, des arts et metiers et du travail.
- Box: 27, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Die schweizerischen Gewerkschaftsverbande im Jahre 1961: Mitgliederbewegung und Sozialleistungen der Gewerkschaften, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Gewerkschaftliche Rundschau, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Landwirtschaft und Landwirtschaftspolitik der Schweiz, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Author: Wilhelm Bickel
- Box: 27, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: GATT: What is it, what it does, how it works, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Author: General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (Organization)
  - Item 2: List of Periodicals Abstracted, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Role of Gatt in Relation to Trade and Development, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Box: 27, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: CIS Classification: Guide to the Card Service, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Author: International Occupational Safety and Health Information Centre
  - Item 2: National and International Legislation Required to bring the activities of Multinational Companies under Social Control, 1974; Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: AALC Geneva June, 1967, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Author: African-American Labor Center
- Box: 27, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: For a Sociological Concept of Charisma, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Author: William H. Friedland
  - Item 2: Political, Economic and Social Resolutions, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Resolution on Finance, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Resolutions on Organization, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Speech by the Hon M.M. Kamaliza, M.P., General Secretary, National Union of Tanganyika Workers, Given at NUTA's Annual Congress held in Dar Es Salaam between 24th March, 1965 - 31st March, 1965, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Co-operation, Conflict, and Conscription: TANU-TFL Relations, 1955-1964, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The Institutionalization of Labor Protest in Tanganyika and some resultant problems, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: The Report of the General Secretary Given at the First General Meeting of NUTA, held in Dar-Es-Salaam, March 24th-31st, 1965, 1966; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Author: National Union of Tanganyika Workers
  - Item 9: The Rules of the National Union of Tanganyika Workers (Constitutions), Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Box: 27, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Report of the Presidential Commission on the National Union of Tanganyika Workers, 1967; Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Author: Tanzania. Presidential Commission on the National Union of Tanganyika Workers
- Box: 27, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Labour Services in Thailand, 1961; Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Author: Thailand. Krom Prachasongkhro
- Box: 27, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: An Overview of the History of Labor in Trinidad from 1498 up to the Origin of the Trade Union Movement in 1937, Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Author: Wilfred Harricharan
  - Item 2: General Industrial Conditions and Labour Relations in Trinidad, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Author: F.W. Dalley
  - Item 3: General Industrial Conditions and Labour Relations in Trinidad, Report, 1954; Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Trinidad and Tobago: An Economic Survey, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Box: 27, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Tunisian Tragedy: Bourguiba Crushes Free Unions, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Author: Ahmed Tlili
- Box: 27, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Foreign Labor Information: Labor in Turkey, 1959; Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Author: United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 2: Social Changes in Mustapha Kemal Ataturk's Turkey, 1958; Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Author: Prof. Z. Findikoglu
    Notes: research paper
  - Item 3: Turk-Is, The Confederation of Turkish Trade Unions: What it is, what it does, how it works, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Author: Turk-Is (Organization)
  - Item 4: Turk-Is, The Confederation of Turkish Trae Unions: What it is, what it does, how it works, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Box: 27, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Co-operation in Uganda, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    Author: E.S. Kamulegeya and A.E. Elogu
  - Item 2: I.L.O. Inter-Regional Seminar on Co-operation: Uganda, 1962; Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Uganda: An Economic Survey, 1964; Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Herdsman, Parts I-IV, 1965; Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    Author: Elizabeth Marshall Thomas
    Notes: article for the New Yorker
- Box: 28, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Some Labor Problems of Industrialization in Egypt, 1956; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Author: F.H. Harbison, I.A. Ibrahim
    Notes: reprinted article
  - Item 2: United Arab Republic, N.I.M.D. 1962-63, 1963; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Author: Ma'had al-Qawmilil-Idarah al-'Ulya (Egypt)
- Box: 28, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Informe Economico Annual del JefeComisionado del Trabajo, 1951; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Derecho Laboral. Abril-Junio 1955, Tomo XI - N. 62, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: El Movimiento Sindical Latino Americano (sus virtudes y sus defectos), 1929; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Author: Por A. Losovsky
  - Item 4: Instituto Uruguayo de Educacion Sindical, 1964; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: C.N.T. declariacion de principios programa y estatutos, 1967; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Author: Convencion Nacional de Trabajadores
  - Item 6: C.S.U. Ante La Huelga Traicionada, La Verdad del Conflicto Municipal, 1960; Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Uruguay: A Little Historic Narration, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Uruguay: A Little Historic Narration, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Box: 28, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Jornada, 1966; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: 12 de Octobre de 1966, Ano IV, No. 116
  - Item 2: Jornada, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: 15 de Marzo de 1965, Ano III, No. 68
  - Item 3: Jornada, 1965; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Jornada, 1966; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: 16 de Septiembre de 1966, Ano IV, No. 112
  - Item 5: Jornada, 1966; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: 21 de Octobre de 1966, Ano IV, No. 117
  - Item 6: Jornada, 1966; Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Notes: 9 de Noviembre de 1966, Ano IV, No. 119
- Box: 28, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Revolucion democratica en america latina, 1964; Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Author: Romulo Betancourt